- Did you get through ? - No .
- What did you buy ? - A Fizz Pop .
I asked for fruit . It 's healthier .
It 's healthier ! Let 's go .
No luck ?
She 's not answering .
What should we do now ? Go back to Grandma 's ?
No way ! They would laugh at me . I can 't go back there .
Let 's go . Let 's go to Constantia .
- Just go ? Without a call ? - It 's fine . I will deal with it .
Listen , Luthando .
Please pick up our child tomorrow and drop her off .
Wow ! You want me to leave Gugulethu
and be back here tomorrow ?
Please . I don 't have a car . You know this .
And public transport here stops at 6 : 00 a.m.
You know I am not a morning person .
Can 't you ask this white woman to lend you a car ?
I am sure there are plenty in this massive yard !
I 'd have to leave there at 5 : 00 a.m. tomorrow .
- Come on , bro . - 5 : 00 a.m. !
She 's taking a while .
She must be busy .
Hello .
Sisi .
Hello , Sisi . It 's me .
Who is me ?
It 's Tsidi , Sisi .
Tsidi ? What brings you here ?
Aren 't you supposed to be in mourning ?
Yet you 're here .
Please open for me ?
Tsidi , I 'm asking .
I 'll explain when I come in , Sisi .
I am with my child , please open .
Well , okay . Come in .
Okay .
What is it , young lady ? Just showing up ?
At least call before showing up . Then I can expect your arrival .
But you don 't . You just rock up .
This way .
Madam is sleeping . Let 's keep it down .
I don 't usually open the door . There are beggars out there .
Mama ! Come and see .
Why didn 't you reach out to Winnie 's father first ?
- Look , Mama . - Come this way .
Keep it quiet .
Madam is sleeping .
Mama , why are we going this way ?
Because Granny stays here .
Come this side .
Where is Luthando , since you 're here with me ?
What room is this , Mama ?
Let me see what I can get you to eat from the kitchen .
Are you hungry , Winnie ?
Yes , I 'm hungry , Grandma .
Okay , I 'll go find something to eat .
- Okay . - Can we stay ?
Yes , you can .
But you know the rules of the house .
I 'll be back . Going to the kitchen .
Mama , what are the rules ?
I want to know them .
Don 't worry about that .
Please tell me so I don 't get in trouble .
So , when you get into the house ,
you can 't run .
You can 't just touch the fridge .
You 've got to ask Grandma first .
You can 't go to the pool unaccompanied .
You have go with someone .
And the most important thing ...
Don 't ever go into Madam 's room .
Okay . So we should pretend not to be here
even though we are ?
- Yes . - Okay .
Wow , Tsidi . Winnie is so grown .
She is beautiful .
Light-skinned , just like my aunt .
She was so young when I last saw her .
She 's a grown woman now .
You 're raising her well , my child .
Tsidi , I am talking to you .
I hear you , Sisi .
Oh , poor Grandma .
I 'm sure her funeral was beautiful .
She really was a people 's person .
Poor Grandma .
I am sure you 're hurting ,
but please forgive me
for not being able to make it to the funeral .
- Where are you going Tsidi ? - Getting fresh air .
Fresh air at this time of night ?
I will cover myself .
Wow . When you think you 've seen it all .
My grandchild
You might see me laugh and assume I am happy
Remember I said I 'd show you the things in Grandma 's kist ?
There is this coat . Feel how heavy it is ?
Grandma loved it ! She 'd wear it when it was cold .
Remember how she loved wearing it in winter ?
- Yes . - When she was travelling .
Here are her table cloths .
Wow , she loved them .
See how beautiful this one is ?
This tablecloth is also soft , right ?
And look how big it is !
And then this one , because it is white .
You needed to know that if you placed it soon after eating ,
you needed to fold and soak it in cold water .
Not warm water , cold water .
Grandma would cook ,
and call all her grandchildren ,
and we 'd fill up the house .
She 'd put the tables together
and place this tablecloth on top .
Tsidi , you call this food ?
So mean ! You know you 've eaten all that food , right ?
I am kidding , cuz ! You really cooked well .
Don 't worry , Mam 'Tshawe . Your food was great !
They 're just jealous !
Second In Command ! Of course you 'd say that .
Stop it ! Don 't be silly .
Tell me , Tsidi ,
what 's the story with you extending the house ?
- This wall ? - Well .
I installed an en-suite bathroom ,
and now I will extend the walls to enlarge the room .
- Okay ! - You see .
Who did you consult with ?
Was I supposed to consult someone ?
Yes .
There are people here , Tsidi !
You can 't just do anything in this house
without consulting us .
I consulted Mama , brother .
The one I lived with here , alone . Get it ?
Tsidi really has no respect for us .
Mama !
Wake up !
Oh , Lord ! Where 's your father ?
Mama , we will be late for school !
Tsidi , talk to the child . She 's loud .
Wait . Okay . Sisi ! I hear you . Alright !
Oh !
Sorry I 'm late . Traffic was a mess .
Why didn 't you tell me you were going to be late ?
It wouldn 't make a difference . I was already on my way .
It 's not like you have plan B.
What plan B ? You 're my plan B.
You 're going to drop her off as well , aren 't you ?
Matsidiso ! Why all this up and down ?
Why can 't she just stay with me ?
That 's not happening .
" Up and down " is you coming to pick up your child !
- Such a waste of petrol ! - Oh , stop it .
Just go ! The kid is late .
She 'll get detention for no reason .
We 're leaving .
- Bye-bye ! - Bye .
- Smile ! - Go away !
- Just go . It 's late ! - Smile !
Hey , wow !
See what I got myself into , being with you ?
Radebe .
Bhungane .
Mthimkhulu . Ngelengele .
Mashwabada owashwabadel inkomo neempondo zayo .
Grandma , forgive me .
Forgive me for the way I left the house .
Forgive me for arguing with Uncle
before your ceremony had been completed .
Forgive me for taking your coat
before your clothes had been distributed .
I am here
at Mama 's workplace with my child .
Please be with me .
Please protect me .
You know how I feel about this place .
Please be with me , Ma Radebe .
Protect me , Ngelengele .
Who are you to discipline my child ?
Who am I ?
That 's my child ! Don 't you have a mouth ?
Can 't you speak to her with your mouth ?
- Here she is , crying ! - It 's all drama .
- What drama ? - The same that you 're full of !
- This is my home , you hear ? - Home ? When were you last here ?
I am not going anywhere !
Hey , girls !
Tsidi , Xoliswa . Be quiet !
As you know , my girl ,
I am the only one left among Mama 's children .
Toto will come and live with you in this house .
Yes .
This is for your own protection .
You might as well be kicking me out .
- How will I live here with Toto ? - That is the end of it !
There shall be no argument about it .
This is for your own protection .
This will not change .
Mam 'Tshawe think about this .
There 's nothing to think about , S 'phe !
Please , Tshiwo .
Please , Mdange . Cuz !
No , Tsidi . Radi 's coat !
Please , cuz .
Let 's go , Winnie . I am taking this coat !
Tsidi , the distribution ceremony hasn 't happened yet .
You 'll get bad luck , Tsidi .
Sisi , did you see that dog ?
- A dog ? - Yes .
What dog are you on about ?
The one from here . With blue eyes .
It died ages ago .
Diane was never the same after it died .
Where is Diane ?
Diane is in her room . She 's unwell .
Okay , what 's wrong with her ?
She is just old .
You do know that you 're old too , right ?
I know that .
I 'm not unaware of it .
Wow . The way you sprint when she calls .
Of course ! Diane does everything for me .
Everything I do is for you and your brother .
Hey , Tsidi , what are you doing ...
in Gcinumzi 's room ?
Where is that Stuart of yours ?
Gcinumzi comes to see Diane and I whenever he gets a chance .
I wonder if it would be to see you or his real mother , Diane .
You love stirring trouble .
- Hi , baby ! - Hello !
- I got 80 out of 80 ! - Who just dropped you off ?
Hannah 's mother .
Who 's Hannah 's mother ?
Where was your dad ?
- He didn 't arrive . - Oh , Luthando !
How can you just let a white woman ...
Her name is Samantha . Samantha .
See , you don 't even know her name !
How could you give away our child ?
I didn 't give her away !
So what do you call what you did ?
She was happy to go with those people .
She was happy because she 's a child , and it 's a fancy car !
What if she hadn 't made it home ?
I would need to go looking for her .
Where would I begin ? Where would I look ?
Who would I say she 'd been with ?
If you were being a responsible adult ,
you would know where she lives .
You don 't know where she lives !
Winnie !
Are you okay ? Did you hurt yourself ?
What 's happened now , Tsidi ?
You don 't watch this child !
You see what 's happened now ?
I do watch her ! She 's just a child .
It 's a mistake ! She was playing !
Look , it 's broken now ! Wow , Tsidi .
- You 're so ungrateful ! - Ungrateful ? Why ?
You 're not bothered at all .
Not bothered ? Fine , I 'll pay for your bell .
- You have no respect . - She is just a child !
What 's there to be grateful for ?
She 's hosting you here !
This Diane of yours doesn 't love you .
She just wants your hands and strength !
Hey , Tsidi ! Where are you going ?
I am talking to you ! Where are you going ?
To Gcinumzi 's room .
How can you go in there , who did you ask ?
I won 't stay in that tiny shell of yours .
- I 'll phone Ross . - Phone if you want .
I 'll phone the police .
- You want me arrested ? - Yes .
For wanting to stay in an empty house ?
You 're always going on about how nice your madam is .
And she is . You 're silly , Tsidi .
- Mama ? - Yes , baby .
Why don 't you like this house ?
I like it .
It is big and beautiful .
- You like it , Sisi ? - Yes .
It 's not that Mama doesn 't like this house .
But it seems this house doesn 't like Mama .
Get it ?
But how ?
- Mama grew up coming here , Sisi . - Yes .
So , when I 'm here ...
I get many memories .
Bad memories .
Okay .
- But you like it here , right ? - Yes .
Who are these people ?
That 's me .
You .
And Grandma .
We all look so beautiful , my girl .
And this house we live in is so beautiful .
You want to stay with Grandma ?
Yes .
We 'll stay a bit longer .
Okay .
Here .
- Perfect . - Yup .
Please be with me , Ma Radebe .
There is no one else I can seek refuge in .
You 're my only hope .
Sisi ?
Why are you in the dark ?
Mavis ?
Mavis !
Mavis .
Mavis , please come and open !
Please come and open the door !
Mavis !
Mavis , your door is locked !
Please come and open the door !
Mavis open the door !
Open it !
Mavis please open !
Come and open !
Eat your porridge . You 've only eaten your orange .
Okay .
Who is this , Winnie ?
I just drew her in .
This is a family picture , right ?
- Yes . - Is she your family ?
- No . - So why put her here ?
No , Tsidi , that looks like that photo of young Diane .
Are we Diane 's family ?
No , Tsidi . The child was just drawing .
It 's not just a drawing . She made a family portrait .
Why put white people in our family ?
She likes Diane .
We have no white relatives . This was for the family .
- Bye , Mama . - Is that Hannah 's mother ?
Let 's go out together . I want to meet this ...
No . You 're still in your pyjamas .
She is right . You can 't go out like this .
I 'll walk her to the car .
Hey , Granny ! Today we 're going to play with slime .
I 'm so excited !
There is nothing wrong with this machine .
It could be that you don 't know how to use it .
I told you not to break Diane 's stuff .
Sisi ? The dishes in the sink ?
I washed them .
Well , here they are .
Diane , thank you very much
for letting my daughter stay in the house .
I don 't know how to thank you .
You know that one is so cheeky !
You are right , Diane .
She 's just like her father .
Hah , Diane !
This tea ! It 's taking a while .
Hey ! These are Diane 's things .
How can you use Diane 's things ?
It 's fine . I 'll wash them when we 're done .
- I don 't use Diane 's cups . - Why ?
These are Diane 's things , Tsidi .
Why not ?
I don 't use them . I have my own cup .
No , it 's fine . I have already warmed these .
These are the things that I like .
We 'll use those mugs later . Here is my cup .
I 'm trying to explain that I heated those ones .
Just do what I asked you to do , Tsidi !
I did it how you like it .
I warmed the cups , heated the milk .
Don 't ever use Diane 's things again .
- Did she order you not to ? - Here 's my cup , Tsidi .
She has you living under apartheid !
It 's not about apartheid , Tsidi .
I just like this cup .
And stop talking to me about apartheid .
But that 's how you choose to live .
Is it you doing this or is it your madam ?
Tsidi , I like my job and I like Diane .
You like her way too much . It 's abnormal .
Wait a second ! Wait .
It sounds like Diane is calling me .
No , Diane is not .
She 's calling me . I heard her .
What you 're doing is not normal , Sisi !
Mother of Winifred !
Are you okay , bro ?
I am okay . Are you okay over there ?
This house ,
it 's weighing heavy on me .
When I try to tell Sisi ,
she doesn 't get it .
I don 't know how to approach her in a way that she 'll get .
Why don 't you ask that coconut , Stuart ?
Where would I start with that coconut ?
I 'd need Google just to communicate !
Don 't put me through that .
I can 't ...
I 'm going to sleep , baby .
Wait , am I disturbing you ?
- No . - Okay , I will call you .
Hey ?
- You 'll phone me ? - I will call you later , okay .
No , feel free !
Go have fun , dude ! It 's cold .
Go and cuddle somebody !
Haha , so silly !
Cool .
- Mama . - Hello .
I saw graves down there !
Stop it , nothing like that there .
She is telling the truth .
There are graves up there in the garden .
No way !
They belong here .
These people bought this land long ago .
They 've lived here long .
- No , Sisi . - So they did everything here .
Even their workers were buried there .
- They buried workers ? - Yes .
I don 't think that 's even legal .
It is legal . This is their land .
Wow .
If you could change anything in this house ,
what would you change ?
I don 't think I would change a thing here .
How long has this house been like this ?
All these years , you 'd change nothing ?
There is nothing I would change . It is Diane 's house .
But you say this is your family .
It is my family , but I can 't just change things .
She should tell me to change a chair or a table .
I have no right to just do what I want .
Okay .
Let me just ...
No , Sisi ! You 're off duty today .
Diane is calling me .
She shouldn 't call you when you 're off duty .
You 're not her slave .
She doesn 't even give you a raise , this Diane .
None of your business !
Sisi . May I please have Gcinumzi 's number ?
What do you need Gcinumzi 's number for ?
Just so I can find him if I need him .
I don 't have it . He 's the one who calls me .
I should phone , but I don 't want to disturb him .
Okay .
Madam ! Diane !
Madam , are you alright ?
Diane ! Madam !
What 's going on ?
Did ma 'am have a stroke ? Or a heart attack ?
Shall we phone Grant or Ross ?
Tsidi , we won 't be phoning Ross or a doctor .
Diane is going to be okay .
Do you understand , Tsidi ,
that Diane is my problem ?
How can she be your problem ?
You 're old . You 're not qualified to ...
Okay , let 's rather call Gcinumzi .
We won 't be phoning Gcinumzi , Tsidi .
I told you , Diane is my problem .
My burden . I will look after her .
How , Sisi ? How ?
Tsidi , you don 't understand any of this .
Do you get that if Diane is placed in elderly care
we 'll have nowhere to go ?
Do you understand that without Diane here
I will have nowhere to go ?
You and your child will have nowhere to stay ?
What do you want me to do , Tsidi ?
There is no other home besides this one .
This is my home , Tsidi .
You don 't understand what 's going on here , Tsidi .
You don 't understand the pain we 're facing right now .
What will we do if Diane dies ? What will we do ?
Listen , Sisi .
I 'm sorry for the way I have been behaving .
It 's just that I am still heartbroken .
I miss Grandma .
I also miss her too .
- But we 'll be okay , right ? - Yes .
- Do you forgive me ? - Yes .
Thank you .
- I love you , okay ? - Love you too .
- Coming now , okay ? - Okay .
Sisi , you shouldn 't be using sugar .
Oh . You know , you 're right .
Do you see why I don 't use Diane 's things ? Look now .
Sisi , please forgive me for saying that Gcinumzi
only comes here to see Madam , not you .
You know , Tsidi ,
this Gcinumzi issue , I didn 't give him up .
I didn 't give him up to Diane .
It was my wish that she 'd help me with Gcinumzi ,
so he could have a good life
and a decent education .
- Are you okay , Mama ? - Yes .
I 'm tired .
Of course you 're tired .
You 're too old for this big house .
Oh please ! I will not die . Switch off the stove .
It 's good to relax after a busy day .
An average day , but a busy day .
These fellows wearing the warm coats
spend a good part of each day just searching for food .
I acquire this field of yours which you love .
I eat and carouse in it .
I drink and plough in it .
I reap in it .
I copulate in it .
I do not perish in it ...
for my magic is powerful in it .
Mommy .
Can I please have R50 for the school trip ?
What school trip ?
You didn 't tell me about any trip .
I did tell you Mommy ,
like a month ago .
But ... Sorry , I don 't have it . Sorry .
But , Mama !
Waking me up with all this English , Winnie !
What 's gotten into you ?
I 'm telling you , you didn 't remind me .
But all my other friends have money , and I don 't .
Go to school ! I 've no money .
I 'm telling you , I don 't have it .
There 's nothing I can do .
Come , child , it doesn 't matter . I will give you the money .
Let 's go , your transport is waiting outside .
Oh , Sisi . You helped me with that child .
Yes .
I don 't know what 's got into her .
Because she isn 't that type of person .
Maybe she misses her dad ?
Maybe I should take her for the weekend ?
Don 't you think ?
Tsidi , what 's really happening between you and Luthando ?
Oh , please .
Nothing is going on . We 're just raising our child .
Oh , yeah ?
I really liked him . Shame . I thought he was the one .
But nothing happened , so it doesn 't matter .
It 's clear he wasn 't the one .
It 's like that sometimes .
Life .
You know , standing here ,
looking at you ,
you look just like Mzwandile .
Your height . Just like Mzwandile 's .
And your stubborn nature , Mzwandile 's !
He was just like this .
Didn 't listen .
But wow ! It was lovely .
We 'd go to the movies .
We 'd go to the Kismet ,
returning on a bus , " Two to Mowbray ! "
Hey !
It was lovely , child .
Everyone had a companion .
All of us on the bus . Each of us partnered .
Here next to you would be a couple . And over there .
No singles !
That 'd be " Two to Mowbray , " child !
It was lovely , then .
Mzwandile really made me happy .
He was such a hunk . Even the way he dressed !
He didn 't just throw clothes on .
He wore genuine fabric .
I received so much love from him .
He was my rose .
I 'm imagining him .
And Gcinumzi 's dad ? What kind of person was he ?
Gcinumzi 's dad was my spare wheel .
- You know what , Tsidi ? - Yes ?
Things I would change in this house .
I would change these many tables .
And those ugly dolls .
I don 't know what 's with these old men with beards !
I don 't know what 's going on .
And the cupboards . The house is dark !
So gloomy ! When you enter a room , it 's so dark !
- It 's just so dark ! - So dim !
And all those bells !
And moving all those things when I clean !
Dusting them ...
Expecting someone ?
No .
Hey ! How 's it , Mama ?
Are you well , Gcinumzi , my child ?
Yes , I 'm good .
Oh ! Gcinumzi ! It 's been a while .
Good to be home , Mama .
- Let me make tea . - Thank you .
Hey , Tsidi . How are you ?
I 'm fine .
Ah , jeez , this looks nice .
- What are we making ? - I made some soup .
Yes , I can 't wait !
I know that me and you are not very close ,
and I don 't usually ask you for anything .
But I 'm really worried about Mavis .
Mavis is old ,
and she 's not coping anymore , you know ?
Just the other day Diane fell , and Mavis ...
Wait , Diane fell ? What happened ?
No , she just had a fall .
But Mavis was unable to help her .
So , did you call a doctor ?
She was sleeping .
Listen , let me just go check up on her ,
and I 'll be back , okay ?
- Okay . - Okay .
I 'm not ready .
Listen , it doesn 't have to be all of her ,
only her hands .
How 's Diane ?
Yeah , she 's hanging in there .
Are you going to call Grant or Ross ?
Um ...
I think I 'll just wait and see how the next week or two goes .
I saw this picture of Mavis in library ...
and it had these markings behind it .
It 's a spell .
And the spell talks about a person
becoming a helper to their master in the afterlife .
This is all confusing to me ,
and I know it sounds insane , and it doesn 't make any sense ...
No , Tsidi . Look , um ...
I 'm also worried about Mavis .
I think she 's been working for too long now ,
and I think it 's about time she slows down
and considers her own needs .
Exactly .
And yeah , I know about her high blood pressure .
Yeah , I 'll talk to her .
- Thank you . - No problem .
Thank you so much .
Mama , there 's no easy way to say this .
But Diane 's health has been deteriorating
faster than we had expected .
It 's safe to say that she will be leaving us soon .
Everything 's going to be okay .
Alright ?
You 've been a part of this family as much as I have .
And you 've done so much work .
I think it 's ...
I think it 's time for you to rest now .
Mama , listen to me .
You don 't have to worry .
You 'll be taken care of , Mama .
Mommy .
What are you doing ?
Mama , I need help .
It 's bad , Mama .
I don 't know what is going on here .
I don 't know if I 'm losing my mind .
All I know , Mama ,
there is a bad spirit here .
The dark spirit is surrounding us .
I can 't live with my child in a place like this .
Please help me .
Please protect me .
Please help me , Radebe .
I have nowhere else to turn to .
Help me , Radebe . Help me , Bhungane .
You might see me laugh and assume I am happy
Mama ?
If you were to see my heart , I am unhappy
You might see me laugh and assume I am happy
My heart aches
I am unhappy I am unhappy
Mama ?
Luthando , listen ! Please come .
Please come and fetch Winnie and I.
Please ! Please come at once !
Winnie ? Winnie !
Come , Sisi ! Are you okay , my child ?
Please go and pack , Sisi . We must go !
Mama ! I don 't want to pack .
Tsidi , what 's going on ?
I spoke to Mama .
I can 't stay . We must leave . Go and pack , my girl .
Tsidi , since Grandma died , everything about you is odd .
Always in her coat . In pyjamas all day .
You fail to understand . She was my mother .
She was a mother to me . You don 't know me !
You 're absent ! I have no birth mother !
- Tsidi , calm down . - I will not calm down !
My birth mother raises white kids in the suburbs !
I 'm staying !
I 'm not going anywhere !
No !
Tsidi , what the hell ? The security company called .
What 's going on ?
Hey !
I 'm telling Sisi that ... Hey you !
I 'm trying to tell Sisi we need to leave here ...
Go to Gugs with your noise ! We don 't do this here !
Gugs ? Because that 's where I belong ?
I don 't deserve these free , safe spaces ...
Don 't be so dramatic for once and listen to me .
I 'm dramatic ? This place will kill her !
- I will not stop ! I will not ! - What 's going on here ?
- You stay out of this ! - Hey you , back off .
Tsidi , you have lost it .
Lost it ? You 're the lost one , Stuart !
What 's going on ?
I 'm trying to tell Mama it 's dangerous here !
People get killed and buried here !
Mama , I don 't want to go back to that dirty , stinky place !
Matsidiso ! Why are you hitting the child ?
Why are you hitting the child ?
What is your problem , dude ?
- It 's not my fault ! - Not your fault !
Nothing is ever your fault !
People are bewitched or brainwashed .
But nothing 's your fault !
I 've had it with you and your family ! Jesus !
Come , baby .
Baby ? We 'll stay in Gugs , okay ?
Luthando .
- Luthando , give me my child ! - Do you hear me ?
Matsidiso ! Winnie will stay with my mom .
She 'll be looked after . You can visit .
But for now , fix your family issues .
Winnie , please get out of there !
Give me my child .
You 're going crazy . You need help .
Open that car , Luthando !
Bring my child ! Open that car !
This is too much .
Dragging me into her family 's madness .
Give me this child !
Luthando !
Seriously , Tsidi !
Are you alright , my baby ?
You 'll be alright ? Sorry , my baby .
You 'll be alright . Mom will be alright .
Give me my child !
Tsidi ?
Tsidi , get up .
Tsidi , you alright ?
What 's going on ?
Tsidi ? Can you hear me ?
What 's happening to you ?
Mavis .
Diane is going to be leaving us tonight .
You 've been a part of this family for so long and ...
just trust Diane 's decision .
You don 't have to worry , Mavis .
I 'll make it quick .
No , no , no !
Gcinumzi , what are you doing ?
Gcinumzi !
Let go , mama !
Gcinumzi ! Why , my child ?
Don 't die , Gcinumzi !
Don 't die , my child !
Gcinumzi !
Come , Tsidi , help me ! Gcinumzi .
Sisi ?
I acquire this field of yours which you love .
I eat and carouse in it .
I drink and plough in it .
I do not perish in it .
For my magic has power in it .
Diane , you would do this to me ?
Hey , Diane ! How could you do this ?
Get off , you witch ! Fuck off !
I 'm so sorry .
Please forgive me , my child .
Shh .
Be strong . Get up , my child .
We 've got work to do here . It 's time to get up .
Get up , my child .
I 'm sorry . Get up .
Hi .
Hello .
- Alright ? - Mm-hmm .
And then ? What 's up with the maid 's uniform ?
Oh , stop it ! It is what it is .
- Cool . - Okay , cool .
- Bye , Winnie ! - Bye .
- Bye ! - Bye .
Hi , Diane , how are you ?
You look very good today .
Guess what ?
There 's a phone from Ross and Grant . From Australia .
Mavis .
No , she 's fine . She 's just tired .
Everything 's under control here the other side .
Yeah , and how are you and your children ?
Yes .
Wow , I would be very happy to come there to visit .
How old is the other one ? Um ...
Jason , how old is he ?
Yeah .
Yeah , I remember .
Yes , Mavis .
You always know just what to say , hey ?
But thank you for looking after her .
And we are looking after ourselves ,
and you must look after yourself too .
Don 't worry , my baby , we are .
Okay , we 'll chat soon . Thank you for everything .
Bye , Grant , speak soon .
Okay , bye .
Ross . Ross !
Mom 's fine .
Everything 's cool . Mavis has got it under control .